漫威《神盾局特工》前情回顧
Previously on "Marvel's Agents Of S.H.I.E.L.D."...
想要不死  就只能融入這里  努力工作
The only way to not die is to blend in and work hard,
沒有這個  就根本做不到
and you can't do either of those things without Matrix.
每個人都要扮演一個角色
Everyone has a role to play
才能讓燈塔不會分崩離析
to keep the Lighthouse from falling apart.
他不非得死的
He didn't have to die.
總有人得死
Somebody did.
卡塞亞斯歡迎你來到他的套房
Kasius welcomes you to his suites.
失一命  得一命
A life taken, a life earned.
你有什么毛病
What is wrong with you?!
你必須
You must...
學會
learn...
靜默
silence.
維吉爾提到了關于我們的故事
Virgil mentioned stories.
我想看看他住的地方
I'd like to see where he lived,
看能不能找到線索表明他對我們有什么打算
see if we can find any clues as to what his plan for us was.
維吉爾總把這個放在拖曳船上
Virgil always kept this in the trawler.
說世界哪一天或許會恢復這個模樣
Said the world might look this way again someday.
這樣的地球還有拯救的希望嗎
Do you see an Earth that can be saved?
已經太遲了
It's too late.
地球已經被震碎了
It's already been quaked apart.
漫威出品
這個印花在都城可是很時髦的
The print is considered quite fashionable in the capitol.
錫納拉
Sinara.
我就知道我們尊貴的客人已經等不及了
I knew our esteemed guest couldn't bear to wait any longer.
卡塞亞斯  感謝你安排了如此
Kasius, how kind of you to arrange such a...
熱烈的歡迎
warm welcome.
這只是日常而已
Just an everyday affair.
想喝一杯嗎
Would you like a drink?
地球人管這個叫馬提尼
The Terrans call it martini.
發酵的糖什么的
Fermented sugars and the like.
我是代表芭莎夫人前來的
I'm here on behalf of the Lady Basha.
她表示遺憾
She sends her regrets.
如果她知道我們
Well, perhaps if she knew
準備了最好的地球美食
how we prepared the best of Earth's cuisine --
她還是喜歡在自己的艦上用餐
She prefers dining on her own ship.
她無意冒犯
She means no disrespect.
不會
No.
當然不會
Surely, none taken.
當然  芭莎夫人對儀式非常期待
Of course, Lady Basha very much looks forward to the ceremony.
她有  很高的期望
She has... high expectations.
絕不會讓她失望
To be exceeded.
泰伊  你現在該跟我說點
Tye, you now have the opportunity
關于儀式的好消息了
to give me good news about our ceremony.
珍瑪  我們遇到麻煩了
Jemma, we have a problem.
為了你自己  我希望你能把它解決
And for your sake, I pray you can fix it.
神盾局特工
第五季 第三集
更新浪費了我的時間和代幣
The Renewal lost me time and tokens!
如果我們不追趕上進度
So if things don't start picking up around here,
我自己也要做更新了
I'm gonna be doing some renewing of my own!
都聽明白了嗎
Is that understood?!
我覺得我也許不該信吉爾
Thinking I may have been wrong to trust Grill.
這就叫話說得太輕吧
This is what we call an understatement, no?
不然我們會被槍擊的
Well, the alternative was getting shot.
至少黛西沒有被困在這里
At least Daisy's not trapped in here.
科爾森  小心點
Coulson, be careful.
他們一直盯著呢
They're always watching.
我知道  但是維吉爾把這個藏了起來
I know, but Virgil hid this thing.
我得搞清楚原因
I got to figure out why.
他這么做是因為這個鐵皮罐會把人逼瘋
He did it because this tin-can place makes people crazy!
新來的
New girl!
快點干活
Work faster!
我來告訴你什么叫快  你這個
I'll show you fast, you --
悠悠球
Yo-Yo.
他電我
He zapped me!
好了
Come on.
門上有機關
The door's rigged.
你真以為那么做會有用嗎
Did you really think that was gonna work?
我覺得至少得試試
Thought I'd give it a shot.
好吧
Well...
我不喜歡這樣
that don't fly with me.
我不會容忍
You see, I don't tolerate
揩油的  偷懶的  和挑事的
skimmers or laggers or agitators.
聽見沒
Hear that?!
只要你還欠我債
As long as you owe me...
你就是我的
I own you.
他們在哪
Where are they?
我們應該在大集市會合的
We were supposed to meet up at the Exchange.
出事了
Something's wrong.
也許他們終于聽了我的建議  融入了這里
Or they finally took my advice to evaporate into this place.
他們之前在找西蒙斯
They were looking for a way to find Simmons.
-我得去找他們  -你說過了
- I got to track them down. - So you said.
你不覺得你在轉移話題嗎
Don't you think you're kind of deflecting
回避我跟你說的...
from what I told you about...
我沒轉移話題  因為那事我沒做
I'm not deflecting 'cause I didn't do it.
那就是轉移話題
Yeah, that's what deflecting is.
我怎么可能把整個世界震碎
How could I split the world apart?
我的能力沒有那么強
My powers aren't that strong.
我沒有那么強
I am not that strong.
也許現在還沒有  但你最終會的
Maybe not yet, but you will be.
你怎么知道
And how do you know that?
因為地球  從圓到缺
Because planet Earth went from smooth to chunky,
就是震波女干的
and Quake is the one who did it.
那你不覺得我會記得嗎
And you don't think I'd remember that?
根據多重宇宙論這是可能的
Well, actually, not according to the multiverse theory.
你可能從沒聽說過
You probably never heard of it,
但量子物理學有個理論
but in quantum physics, there's a theory
每一個世界都對應著無數平行世界
that, for every universe, there are infinite parallel universes.
所以在我的世界里  你毀了地球
So in my universe, you destroyed the planet.
也許那沒在...
Maybe that just hasn't happened in --
剛剛這個是在哪個宇宙里發生的
So what universe did that just happen in?
我的還是你的
Mine or yours?
不
Oh, no.
怎么回事
Talk to me.
-剛剛進行了更新  -什么
- There's been a Renewal. - A what?
有三個人死了
Three people are dead.
別暴走
Just hold your freak-out.
不是你朋友
It wasn't your friends, okay?
他們可能藏起來了
They're probably hiding,
我一開始就建議他們那樣做的
which is what I advised them to do from the get-go.
好好  那他們會藏在哪兒
Okay, okay. So where would they be hiding?
我不知道  他們是你的朋友
I don't know. They're your friends.
這是你家
And this is your home,
你知道這里的每個人每件事
where you know everyone and everything that's in here.
有一個空位是在吉爾的打撈部
One of the vacancies came from Grill's salvage.
也就是說那里會有個空職
That means there's an opening.
他也許會接收散人  你可以從那兒找起
He might take in strays. I'd start there.
這都是從擦鞋的那兒知道的
You got all that the from shoe guy?
擦鞋的什么都知道
Well, shoe guy knows all.
看來我就該去問他的
Guess I should have asked him in the first place.
別做傻事  拜托
Don't do anything dumb, please.
那樣太蠢了  別再為我冒險了
我那樣做不是為了你
我是想看看辦公室里面是什么樣
I was trying to get a look inside that office.
吉爾把那個平板卷軸藏在了他桌子后的柜子里
Grill's keeping that Scroll in the cabinet behind his desk.
那東西或許能讓我們進入
That thing might get us into the levels
他們關押西蒙斯的那層
where they're keeping Simmons.
他那里還藏了把槍
Well, he's got a handgun in there, too.
人類不允許持槍的
Humans aren't allowed to have guns.
除非是為了聚眾殺人
Except for murder sports, apparently.
關鍵是  我們得謹慎行事
Well, the point being, we need to tread lightly.
悠悠球  如果你能進去
Now, Yo-Yo, if you can get in there,
或許我們可以拿回那個平板卷軸
maybe we can get that Scroll back.
干得不錯  邁克
Nice work, Mack.
看見了嗎  我并不蠢  是偵察
You see? Not stupid. Recon.
偵察
Recon.
拖曳船作業
Trawler run.
很好  很好
Good. That's good.
對  因為我上次差點沒活下來
Yeah, 'cause I barely survived the last one.
帶我一起去
Take me with you.
什么  不
What? No.
帶我一起去
Take me with you.
泰絲
Tess,
你和你的朋友幫了我們忙  得了一命
you and your friend here did us a kindness, taking a life.
對
Yeah.
但你還是欠我雙倍的貨物
But you still owe me a double haul.
是嗎  你之前沒提過
Do I? You never mentioned it.
我需要幾個粉碎工
I'll need a few crushers
如果你希望我拉回一整船的貨
if you want me to pack the belly full on that thing.
有可用的人嗎
Got anyone expendable?
把那個挑事的和他朋友帶走
Take the agitator and his friend.
如果這些討厭鬼卡在了網里  也不算什么損失
No big loss if one of these jokers gets caught in the nets.
你說了算
If you say so.
來吧  你們兩個
Come on, you two.
-求你  -不
- Please -- - No!
你必須學會
You need to learn.
你對她做了什么
What did you do to her?
是她自己做的
She's doing it to herself.
現在她是你的問題了  治好她
It's your problem now. Fix it.
對  他們走了
Yeah, they're gone.
沒事了
It's okay.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
艾比
Abby.
你癲癇發作多久了  艾比
How long have you had seizures, Abby?
跟我說說吧  我是醫生
You can talk to me. I'm a doctor.
你一直都
Have you always --
泰瑞根變異后才成了這樣
Only since Terrigenesis.
你是異人
You're Inhuman.
對
Yes.
要是我沒準備好參加儀式
And if I'm not ready for the ceremony...
我不知道我會怎么樣
I don't know what's gonna happen to me.
等等  你們成了垃圾場之王的契約仆人
So, wait -- you're an indentured servant to the junkyard king?
其他人都去太空行走了
And everyone else is on a space walk.
沒時間解釋了
But there's no time to explain.
他們在追蹤我  別讓人看見你在這兒
They're tracking me. You shouldn't be seen here.
你得走了
You should go.
說得好  我們走吧
That's a great idea. Let's go.
不行  我得留下來
I can't. I need to stay.
我從克里人守衛那兒偷的那玩意
The thing I stole from the Kree guard,
老大把它拿回辦公室了
boss man has it in his office,
但我知道怎么拿到它了
but I think I found a way to get it.
很好
That's good.
要是你能把它拿給我  我或許就能去救西蒙斯
If you can get it to me, maybe I can get to Simmons.
沒錯  你走吧  別走遠
Exacto. So go, but stay close.
新來的
New Girl!
你再慢吞吞  就給我進粉碎機
You get any slower, you're going in the crusher.
我不信任他們
I don't trust them.
我一直覺得維吉爾在揩油
I always thought Virgil was skimming.
反正有人在偷我的東西
Somebody has been stealing from me,
他死了  現在又來了這些新人
so he dies, and now these guys show up?
你覺得他們是他的接班人
You think they're taking over his old racket?
那為什么還派他們做維吉爾的活
So why send them on Virgil's run?
因為你想找證據
'Cause you want to find proof.
不  我要你找證據
No, I want you to find proof.
弗林特  出去啦  孩子
Flint! Clear out, kid.
你不是說我可以在這兒睡嗎
I thought you said I could crash here.
對  但作業時不行
Yeah. Not during operation.
走吧
Come on.
不到24小時
So, less than 24 hours,
你就已經成了囚犯
and you've already been taken prisoner.
-創紀錄了  -差得遠呢
- That a record? - Not even close.
我們還是專注于好消息吧
But let's focus on the positives.
怎么了
So what's going on?
你在里面找到什么了嗎  大偵探
Yeah, you find anything in there, Sherlock?
我認為維吉爾是在做偵查
I think Virgil was doing recon.
你說他總待在拖曳船里
You said he was in the trawler all the time?
我覺得他是在找什么東西
I think he was searching for something.
這些數字  是太空里的物體  對嗎
These numbers, they're objects in space, right?
對  他一直在記錄它們
Yeah. He kept track of them.
這個反復出現
Well, this one kept showing up over and over,
地球的這片碎塊
this one specific part of Earth.
616  是啊
616. Sure.
是比較大的一塊
One of the larger segments.
但是我去過那里
But I've been there.
就是一大塊廢石而已
It's just a chunk of dead rock.
也許他把什么東西藏在那里了
Well, maybe he hid something out that way.
不知道  但我們必須去看看
I don't know. But we have to check it out.
我們來到這里的原因也許就在外面
The answer to why we're here might be out there.
那我們去吧
Then we go.
我倒不想去一個沒人能聽到你叫救命的地方
I'd rather not go where no one can hear you scream,
但是好吧
but... okay.
我想幫你們
I want to help you guys,
但我已經欠了兩批貨
but I'm already on the hook for a double haul.
我不能再干額外的活兒
There's no way I can do a side mission.
這不是額外的活兒  這是我們唯一的任務
This isn't a side mission. It's the mission.
維吉爾為此而死
This is what Virgil died for.
我知道你并不覺得他不重要
I know you don't think he was just expendable.
聽著
Look.
我們得小心點
We got to be careful.
我們得掩藏好行蹤
We got to cover our tracks,
如果有哪怕...
and if there's so much as a hic--
你們怎么突然靜下來了
See how you all just got quiet?
所以我要一起來
That's why I'm coming on this run.
你知道這里的規矩
I mean, you know how it works here.
當然
Of course.
我只是好奇你的具體經歷
I was just curious about your specific experience.
沒什么特別的
It's nothing special.
所有人到了18歲都要經歷
All the 18-year-olds go through it.
我穿過迷霧時  還算比較幸運的
When the mist hit me, I was one of the lucky ones.
幸運  嗯
Lucky. Yeah.
我聽說泰瑞根變異可能會是很有創傷性的經歷
I've heard Terrigenesis can be a traumatic experience.
我只是想著我的家人
I just thought of my family.
離開他們很難過
It was hard to leave them,
但是知道他們會得到獎勵  幫助
but... knowing that they'd be rewarded helped.
那個人
That man...
泰伊
Tye?
他在傷害你嗎
Is he hurting you?
不是
Oh, no.
不是  泰伊一直在幫我
No, Tye's been trying to help me,
教我控制我的異能
teach me to control my gift.
我只是一直都做不到
I just... haven't been able to do it yet.
如果我不能完成儀式
I don't know what will happen to them
我不知道他們會怎么樣
if I can't complete the ceremony.
就是展示你的能力嗎
That's where you demonstrate your abilities.
在那之后  我就能離開這個星球
And then after, I get to go off-planet,
以大使的身份周游銀河系
travel the galaxy as an ambassador.
那就太好了
It's a dream.
所以我必須學會
It's why I have to learn.
我或許能幫上忙
I might be able to help.
你能形容一下你的能力嗎
Can you describe what it is you can do?
可以
Yeah, well, um...
有時我非常輕
sometimes I'm so light,
我的手可以穿過任何東西
my hand can just pass right through things.
但有時  我又像鉛那么重
And then, sometimes, I'm as solid as lead.
你可以控制你的分子密度
You can control your molecular density.
是  但我無法掌控它
Yeah, but I can't control it.
我整個身體  都會變緊密
Everything in me, it just -- it tenses up,
那讓我很痛
and it hurts.
有時唯一能讓這一切停止的辦法
Sometimes the only way I can get it to stop
就是讓泰伊開啟我的阻斷器
is if Tye turns on my blocker.
那東西能抑制你的能力
That thing inhibits your powers?
它能幫到我
It helps me.
他們在幫助我
They help me.
我只是不配
I'm just not worthy of it.
艾比
Abby.
你當然配
You are worthy.
我認識很多異人
I've known many Inhumans,
他們都是花了些時間才能掌控自己的能力的
and every one of them took time to master their abilities.
他們給我時間了
I've had time.
如果我不能在儀式上展示
And if I can't perform at the ceremony...
泰伊說我的家人將受到懲罰
Tye says that my family will be punished.
我根本不在乎我會怎么樣
So I don't -- I don't even care what happens to me.
我需要為他們做到
I need to do this for them.
求你了
Please.
我會幫你的
I'll help you.
邁克在下面分散他的注意呢
Mack keeping him distracted down there?
澤夫非常享受為難他
Zev's enjoying giving him a hard time.
我覺得這可能是我們最后的機會了
I think this might be our last shot.
先不說這場反烏托邦未來恐怖秀到底如何
Say what you will about our future dystopian horror show.
至少風景不錯
It has a nice view.
讓人目眩神迷
Dazzling.
腿怎么樣了
How's the leg?
我不想騙你
I'm not gonna lie.
你覺得我們在那兒會有什么發現嗎
You think we're gonna find something out there?
回去的路
Maybe a way back?
我不知道
I don't know.
或許根本沒有回去的路
Maybe there is no way back.
聽著不像是你會說的話
That doesn't sound like you.
不過是在控制期待
Just managing expectations.
你這是認命
You're being fatalistic.
你知道我從來不相信什么命運  但
Look, you know I'm not big on destiny, but...
或許我們的命運就是在這兒
maybe our destiny's here...
在這個時空  幫助這些人
in this time, helping these people.
我也不是不想幫忙
It's not like I don't want to help.
我想
I do.
但在那之后  我要回家
But after that, I'm going home.
我在"框架"里待了幾周
I spent weeks in the Framework,
被綁在一塊板子上  以為自己是九頭蛇的人
strapped to a board, thinking I was Hydra.
我有資格在自己的床上睡個好覺
I've earned a night in my own bed.
警告  工人穿過警戒線
新來的
New people.
警告  工人穿過警戒線
新來的
New girl!
我干得已經夠快了
I'm going as fast as I can.
過來
Get over here.
你的生物表出問題了
Your Metric's on the fritz.
手臂伸出來
Arm out.
好了
There.
這樣應該可以了
That oughta do it.
別再磨磨蹭蹭的
No more dilly-dallying.
澤夫忙于教訓你們的朋友
Zev's so busy teaching your friend a lesson,
還沒注意到我們偏離航線了
he hasn't noticed we're off course yet.
我們得盡快
We should hurry.
天哪
My God.
有人能幸存下來簡直是奇跡
It's a miracle anybody survived at all.
我忘了我帶著這玩意
I forgot I had this thing.
維吉爾總是這樣做
Virgil would always do this.
說他喜歡看到地球修好后的樣子
Said he liked seeing what Earth will look like when it's fixed.
從來都會帶著它飛行
Wouldn't fly without it.
有一次  他耽擱了我們一個小時
Uh, one time, he delayed us an hour
就為了回他的床鋪拿這個東西
so he could go back to his bunk and get it.
我猜他是迷信
Superstitious, I guess.
或者...
Or...
不是
...not.
這是丟失的那個把手
It's the lost knob.
維吉爾在跟什么人通話
Virgil was talking to someone.
抓到你們了
Busted.
我會很享受的
I'm gonna enjoy this.
你把大家都粘在墻上了嗎
You got everyone secured to the wall?
沒錯
That's right.
很好
Good.
謝謝
Thank you.
我沒辦法
I had to.
你們都被釘在墻上了
You were all pinned to the wall,
到處亂飛  就像桌游里的玩偶
flailing around like a bunch of hungry, hungry hippos.
我自以為要酷一些呢
In my mind, it was cooler than that.
這糟透了
Oh, this is bad.
不止是糟透了
This is beyond bad.
我們做了什么
What did we just do?
采取了必要的行動
We did what we had to.
不  你不懂
No, you don't understand.
我們打了上級
We just attacked a superior.
我們死定了
We're dead.
我們再試一次
Let's try again.
不行的
It's not gonna work.
來吧  你可以的  艾比
Come on. You can do this, Abby.
我沒想要這樣的
I didn't mean to do that.
是啊  但這很厲害
No, but that was impressive.
你很強大
You're powerful.
如果我想做的時候卻做不到就沒用了
Well, not if I can't do it when I actually want to.
你可以的
But you can.
心勝于物
It's mind over matter.
對于你來說  是組成你身體的物質
Or in your case, the literal matter that makes up your body.
想想看這地方
Think of this place.
你看到一張桌子  這個水罐
You see a table, this pitcher,
而外面  有無數的群星
and outside, the stars, millions of them.
所有這些  宇宙的每一部分
All of that, every part in the universe
都由同樣的東西組成  原子  中子  電子
is made of the same thing -- protons, neutrons, electrons.
而這些微小粒子之間是什么呢
And you know what's between those tiny particles?
空間
Space.
無限的空間
Infinite space.
好吧
Okay.
你的身體就像是一個星群
Your body is like a field of stars,
但你很特別
but you're special.
你可以控制群星之間的空間
You can control the space between the stars.
群星之間的空間
The space between the stars.
想像一下
Imagine it.
閉上你的眼睛想象
Close your eyes and imagine it.
現在再試一次
Now try again.
我從未能像這樣平穩地保持住
I've never been able to hold it steady like this before.
很好
That's good.
記住這種感覺
Just remember this feeling.
我沒控制住  我
I lost it. I --
沒關系
It's okay.
掌握一種能力需要數月
Takes months to master a talent.
也許可以快得多
Or perhaps much less time.
艾比  跟我來
Abby, with me.
什么  別  等等  我們
What-what, no, wait. We're,
我們需要更多時間
We need more time.
最好不要
Let's all hope not.
我很期待你的表現
I look forward to your performance.
你會很棒的  艾比
You'll do great, Abby.
-就算是...  -安靜
- Even just a... - Silence.
你是不是就希望小醫生失敗
Did you set our little healer up to fail
因為我覺得她漂亮
because I think she's pretty?
還是說你真覺得她會成功
Or did you really think she'd succeed?
你想讓我高興
You want to see me happy.
那么告訴我
Then tell me,
珍瑪究竟擁有什么  會如此特別
what does Jemma have that makes her so different...
讓她有能力做到這個
makes her capable to succeed in this?
同情心
Compassion.
我需要問你為什么要拿著那玩意嗎
Do I need to ask what the hell you're doing with that?
現在換你跟我了
So now you're tailing me?
我亂猜一下  你是不會懂的
Shot in the dark -- you won't get it.
因為你太高尚了  我無法理解嗎
Oh, 'cause you're too noble for me to understand?
我們那里  都是互相保護的
Where I come from, we protect each other.
你想硬沖進去
You are storming the castle.
你打算怎么活著做到這一點
Any plan how you're gonna do that alive?
我猜也是
That's what I thought.
我就是干這個的
This is what I do.
我的朋友有生命危險
My friend's life is on the line,
我會想到辦法的
so I'll figure something out.
那就盲目地沖進去嗎
Oh, just all in, totally blind, huh?
就算你有勝算  這也太蠢了
It's a stupid way to play, even if you have a good hand.
你該放長線釣大魚
You should be playing the long game.
-放長線釣大魚  -是的
- The long game? - Yes.
我可以讓你大搖大擺地走進去
I can make it so that you could waltz down there
收到大佬的邀請
with an invitation from the big man,
但那是需要時間的
but that takes serious time.
是需要手腕的
It takes finesse.
或是需要我已經拿到的平板卷軸
Or it takes the Scroll that I have now.
所以謝謝你沒完沒了的建議了  迪克
So thank you for your endless advice, Deke.
你這是要往圓鋸上撞
You are about to walk into a buzzsaw.
你就是擔心會對你有不良影響
You're just worried it's gonna blow back on you.
這跟我沒關系
This has nothing to do with me!
如果你去找藍臉人惹事
If you pick a fight with the Blues,
他們會拿我們所有人撒氣
they are gonna take it out on all of us.
今天的更新奪走了三條人命
Today's Renewal was for three people.
明天可能就是30條  死亡在這里經常降臨
Tomorrow could be for 30. Death comes easy here.
所以  我得馬上找到西蒙斯
Which is why I need to get to Simmons now.
如果我是你  就別擋道
So if I were you, I'd get out of my way.
你已經毀掉了這世界一次
You already destroyed the world once.
我不會允許你再做一次了
I am not gonna let you do it again.
她出現了  震波女
So there she is -- Quake...
世界毀滅者
the destroyer of worlds.
不許再那么喊我了
Don't ever call me that again.
我們完了  我說了  就是塊破石頭
We're screwed. I told you, it's a dead rock.
我們白白拿性命冒了險
We just risked our lives for nothing.
他怎么樣了
How is he?
他昏過去了  暫時是的
Oh, he's out cold -- for now.
如果我們知道好歹  或許該讓他不要醒來
If we know what's good for us, maybe he stays that way.
什么意思
What are you getting at?
我是說  我們封閉倉口  然后清倉
I'm saying we seal the hatch, and we dump the load.
澤夫沒能及時趕出來
Zev didn't make it out in time.
就是個意外
It was an accident.
-這是殺人  -是算數
- That's murder. - That's math.
失一命  得一命  這里就這樣
A life spent is a life earned. That's how it works.
你拿獵槍打死一個人時我就看懂了
I got that when you took out a guy with a shotgun.
我是在救她的命
I was saving her life!
什么...
What the...
那是人聲嗎
Is that a voice?
是傳送
It's a transmission.
信號微弱  但是
It's a faint signal, but...
源頭就在我們面前
...the source is right in front of us.
這不可能
That's impossible.
一塊死石頭怎么可能發送信號
How is anything coming from a lifeless rock?
我不知道
I don't know.
可能是反射
It could be reflecting.
對  我覺得你是對的
Yeah, I think you're right.
它只是在616上反彈了出來
It's only bouncing off of 616.
但信號源是
But the, uh, signal's origins...
地球地表
It's coming from the surface of the Earth.
有請芭莎夫人
May I present the Lady Basha.
閣下
Your Excellency.
希望您旅途順利
I pray your journey was not too difficult.
卡塞亞斯
Kasius.
你還真是在這塊石頭上為自己雕刻出了
Well, you have carved out a little life for yourself
一份生活  是吧
on this rock, haven't you?
一點沒錯
Quite literally.
從地表下的石灰巖層
From the deposit of limestones under the surface,
再到死去了十億年的
the crushed skeletons of marine creatures
海洋生物化石
dead a billion years.
您近來可好
And you've been well?
我們還好  雖然這里路途遙遠
We fared well, considering the remote location.
我們都急切地等待您的到來呢
Well, we've been eagerly awaiting your arrival.
怎么回事
What's happening?
現在我們要看她的工作成果了
Now we'll see the fruits of her labor.
親愛的芭莎  希望您喜歡今晚的展示
Basha, my dear, I do hope you enjoy tonight's exhibition.
不  你不能...
No, you can't --
你答應給我一個戰士的
You promised me a warrior.
您會發現  這些異人  不像看上去那么簡單
You'll find, with Inhumans, looks can be deceiving.
希望是的
I hope so.
我可是遠道而來
I've come a long way.
也讓我無比榮幸  還帶來了您的冠軍勇士
And you do me a great honor, bringing along your champion.
也算不上是我的冠軍
He's hardly my champion,
但他在7個星系里殺了13個對手
but he has killed 13 opponents in 7 systems.
這就是你能拿得出手的最好的嗎
This is the best you have to offer?
希望她能找到感覺
Let's all hope she can find her way.
很多我們珍視的生命就指望她的成功呢
So many lives we prize depend upon her success.
令人失望
Disappointing.
想著群星
Just think of the stars.
看來我們的戰士終于找到了感覺
It may be our warrior has found her way.
求你
Please.
驚人
Extraordinary.
你們死定了
You're dead!
我要拿你們喂蟑螂
I'm gonna feed you to the roaches!
聽到了嗎
You hear me?!
找不到靜音鍵
Can't find the mute button.
喂  有人在嗎  收到嗎
Hello? Is anyone out there? Do you read?
不行
Nothing.
我記錄下了傳送  但還是無法發送
I'm recording the transmission, but I still can't make it out.
澤夫是對的
Zev's right you know.
我們都是螳螂食了
We're roach food.
你們會后悔的
You're gonna regret this.
我們會有辦法的  我們總會有辦法的
We'll figure it out. We always do.
你不懂
You don't get it!
如果我們對任務撒謊
The moment we lied about this mission,
就會有人死
someone was gonna die.
不是他  就是我們
It's him or us.
我們不會清倉的
We're not dumping the load.
我必須得趁現在還有機會動手
I've got to while we have the chance.
你要擋我的道嗎
You gonna get in my way?
為那個人渣犧牲你的性命
Sacrifice your lives for that piece of trash?
我們不會犧牲任何人  懂了嗎
We're not sacrificing anyone, you understand?
我們神盾局有自己的一套準則
As S.H.I.E.L.D., we live by a code,
我們不會向你們扭曲的世界觀屈服的
and we're not bending to your twisted world view.
我們的燃油在快速消耗
We're losing fuel, fast!
原本還有六小時的
We had six more hours worth.
澤夫割斷了油管線
Zev cut the fuel line.
梅  能送我們回燈塔嗎
May, can you get us back to the Lighthouse?
可以試試
Yeah, I can try.
傳送訊息記錄得夠多了嗎
You have enough of that transmission recorded?
不夠也得夠了
It's gonna have to be enough.
我們得轉身快跑
Because we need to turn and burn
并祈禱不會遭遇重力風暴
and pray that we don't hit a gravity storm.
做吧
Do it.
我們的機會沒了
There goes our chance.
希望值得
Hope it was worth it.
地球人本是個平凡的種族
The Terrans were such an unremarkable species.
但你把他們的世界改造得很好
You have done well with their world.
要是找不到機會
Well, if I can't find opportunity,
我就自己創造
I make my own.
在這樣一塊破石頭上  也必須如此
Well, you would have to on a grim little rock like this.
我們說好的
As we agreed.
不  艾比  不可以
No, Abby, you can't!
錫納拉  別沖動
Now, Sinara, let's not be rash.
珍瑪展示了她的價值
Jemma demonstrated her worth.
你賣掉了她
You sold her.
如果不是你
And if not for you...
她也不會賣出如此高價
she wouldn't have fetched such a high price.
還有幾箱
Got a few more.
快點
Move it!
我真心以為能行呢
I really thought this would work.
打得愉快  但我還有地方要去呢
This has been fun, but I've got someplace to be.
完全不像我希望的那么隱秘
So not as stealth as I hoped.
這可好
Awesome.
開什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
你們一定是我見過的最蠢的一群人了
You have got to be the dumbest bunch of lugs I have ever seen.
澤夫抓到你們偷運違禁品
Zev catches you smuggling contraband,
你們就叛亂
and then you mutiny?
叛亂  這詞也太夸張...
Mutiny? That's a strong wor--
繼續維吉爾的事業嗎
Picking up where Virgil left off?
我就知道有人在偷東西
I knew someone was stealing.
偷偷藏東西[松鼠]
Squirreling things away.
就好像你知道松鼠什么樣似的
Yeah, like you know what a squirrel is.
閉嘴  挑事的
Shut it, agitator!
我要殺了你們所有人  慢慢折磨死你們
I am gonna kill the lot of you, good and slow!
但我要從你開始
But I'm starting with you.
不是他們  是我
It wasn't them. It was me.
-只有我一人  -泰絲
- Just me. - Tess.
吉爾  他們根本不認識維吉爾
Grill, these people didn't even know Virgil.
你對他的不滿  現在都由我來承擔了
So any gripe you had with him is with me now.
違禁品也是
Same with any contraband.
你想要違禁品
You want contraband?
他有把槍
He has a gun.
槍
A gun?
澤夫拿它威脅我來著
Zev threatened me with it.
大概也威脅了他們
Probably threatened them, too.
如果你想找違禁品  他就有
If you're looking for contraband, he's got it.
不可能  老大
No way, boss.
搜他
Search him.
如果我說錯了  我清楚下場
If I'm wrong, I know the consequences.
不可能  不不
No way. No, no, no, no. No way.
這是你偷的  從別人那里
You stole this. From someone.
不是的  等等
No. Wait. Wait.
人類是不許持有武器的
Humans aren't allowed to have firearms.
我們想告訴你真相  但他是你的人
We wanted to tell you the truth, but he's your guy, and --
我們不希望藍臉人來找你麻煩
We didn't want the Blues to come down on you.
所以我要親自舉報這個違規者
That's why I'm reporting this violator to them myself.
吉爾  不要
Grill, no.
你清楚他們對此的懲罰是什么
You know what their punishment is for this.
讓這成為一個教訓吧
Let that be a lesson.
沒人可以凌駕于規矩之上
No one is above the rules!
你是對的
You were right.
我很少會感到驚訝
It's a rare occasion that I am surprised,
但這算是一次
but count this among them.
我就說她會找下來的
I told you she'd find her way down here.
還會展示她的能力
And demonstrating her powers, no less.
那就是個大規模殺傷性武器
That right there is a weapon of mass destruction,
那個身材嬌小的女人  是獻給您的
tied up in one pretty, little package, all for you.
我們可以回頭再談價錢
We can talk about price later,
但我相信你會很公道的
but I expect that you'll be more than fair.
這就是震波女  世界毀滅者
So, this is Quake, Destroyer of Worlds.
那她怎么可能在這兒
How is it possible that she's here?
重要的是
The important thing is...
她是你的了
she's yours.
我要殺了你
I'll kill you.
我發誓
I swear.
抱歉  甜心
Sorry, sweetheart.
我只是在放長線釣大魚
I'm just playing the long game.
好了  菲爾
All right, Phil.
風景看夠了
Enough sight-seeing.
繼續工作吧
Get back to work.
誰需要睡覺  我來值下一輪班
Who needs some sleep? I'll get the next shift.
少來  你睡得比我們都少
Nice try. You slept less than all of us.
嗯  而且我們反正也得再去做打撈
Yeah, we got to get back to salvage, anyway,
希望這樣可以
so let's hope this does the trick.
肯定是殘存信號
It's got to be remnants.
以前的傳送訊號  在引力場里循環播放
Old transmissions in a gravitational feedback loop.
相信我  是地表傳來的
I'm telling you, it's from the surface.
那不可能
That's impossible.
地表上是無法生存的
Nothing can survive on the surface.
維吉爾  回復
Virgil, come in.
收到嗎
Do you read?
我們已經三天沒有你的消息了
We haven't heard from you in three days.
請回復  維吉爾
Please respond, Virgil.
你找到代表團了嗎
Have you secured the delegation?
他是在說我們  我們就是代表團
He's talking about us. We're the delegation.
不管那是誰  他知道我們來了和我們為什么來
Whoever that is knows we're here, knows why we're here.
那么那里確實有人
So there's someone out there.
我們得找到他們
We need to find them.
我們得找辦法上去
We need to find a way to get up there.
不行  你們不懂
No. You're not listening.
地表上什么都無法生存
Nothing can survive on the surface.
那是他們送人去死的地方
That's where they send people to die.